(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[3],{200:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.r(a);var n=t(0),i=t.n(n),s=t(203),r=t(205),o=[{interviewSet:1,questions:[{id:1,question:"What is html? 1",answer:"html is",example:"<a name=”topsection”>Top</a> <p> - - - - - - - - - - - - </p> <div> - - - - - - - - - - - - </div> <a href=”#topsection”>GO TO TOP</a> ",tip:"tip"},{id:2,question:"What are tags?",answer:"Most of the content of the HTML document is enclosed by starting and ending tags. Various types of tags are available in HTML to add text, image, audio, and video in the document. Each tag is declared by enclosing with less than symbol (<) and the greater than symbol (>). A slash symbol (/) is used in the closing tag. ",example:"\n<p>Hello World!</p>\n<hr/>\n<div>Hello World, again!</div>\n\nHere, three tags are declared which are p, br and div.\n",tip:"hr tag is one type of empty that is used to create a horizontal line in the HTML document. No ending tag is added for this tag and the starting tag is closed by a slash (/).  \n"},{id:3,question:"plm ? ",answer:"html is",example:'<img src="picture.gif" width="300" height="200"  usemap="#imgmap">\n\n<map name="imgmap">\n  \t<area shape="circle" coords="75,45,5" href="flower.htm" >\n \t<area shape="rect" coords="10,5,90,150" href="bird.htm" >\n</map>\n',tip:"tip"},{id:4,question:"da?",answer:"html is",example:"example",tip:"tip"}]},{interviewSet:2,questions:[{id:1,question:"What is html? 2 - 1",answer:"html is",example:'<img src="picture.gif" width="300" height="200"  usemap="#imgmap">\n\n<map name="imgmap">\n  \t<area shape="circle" coords="75,45,5" href="flower.htm" >\n \t<area shape="rect" coords="10,5,90,150" href="bird.htm" >\n</map>\n',tip:"tip"},{id:2,question:"What are tags?",answer:"Most of the content of the HTML document is enclosed by starting and ending tags. Various types of tags are available in HTML to add text, image, audio, and video in the document. Each tag is declared by enclosing with less than symbol (<) and the greater than symbol (>). A slash symbol (/) is used in the closing tag. ",example:"\n<p>Hello World!</p>\n<hr/>\n<div>Hello World, again!</div>\n\nHere, three tags are declared which are p, br and div.\n",tip:"hr tag is one type of empty that is used to create a horizontal line in the HTML document. No ending tag is added for this tag and the starting tag is closed by a slash (/).  \n"},{id:3,question:"What is html? 2 - 2",answer:"html is",example:"<a name=”topsection”>Top</a> <p> - - - - - - - - - - - - </p> <div> - - - - - - - - - - - - </div> <a href=”#topsection”>GO TO TOP</a> ",tip:"tip"},{id:4,question:"What is html? 2 - 3",answer:"html is",example:'<img src="picture.gif" width="300" height="200"  usemap="#imgmap">\n\n<map name="imgmap">\n  \t<area shape="circle" coords="75,45,5" href="flower.htm" >\n \t<area shape="rect" coords="10,5,90,150" href="bird.htm" >\n</map>\n',tip:"tip"}]},{interviewSet:3,questions:[{id:1,question:"What is html? 3 - 1",answer:"html is",example:"<a name=”topsection”>Top</a> <p> - - - - - - - - - - - - </p> <div> - - - - - - - - - - - - </div> <a href=”#topsection”>GO TO TOP</a> ",tip:"tip"},{id:2,question:"What are tags?",answer:"Most of the content of the HTML document is enclosed by starting and ending tags. Various types of tags are available in HTML to add text, image, audio, and video in the document. Each tag is declared by enclosing with less than symbol (<) and the greater than symbol (>). A slash symbol (/) is used in the closing tag. ",example:"\n<p>Hello World!</p>\n<hr/>\n<div>Hello World, again!</div>\n\nHere, three tags are declared which are p, br and div.\n",tip:"hr tag is one type of empty that is used to create a horizontal line in the HTML document. No ending tag is added for this tag and the starting tag is closed by a slash (/).  \n"},{id:3,question:"What is html? 3 - 3",answer:"html is",example:'<img src="picture.gif" width="300" height="200"  usemap="#imgmap">\n\n<map name="imgmap">\n  \t<area shape="circle" coords="75,45,5" href="flower.htm" >\n \t<area shape="rect" coords="10,5,90,150" href="bird.htm" >\n</map>\n',tip:"tip"},{id:4,question:"What is html? 3 - 4",answer:"html is",example:"example",tip:"tip"}]}],l=t(408),c=t(406);var d=function(e){var a,t;function n(){for(var a,t=arguments.length,n=new Array(t),i=0;i<t;i++)n[i]=arguments[i];return(a=e.call.apply(e,[this].concat(n))||this).state={doneQuizData:[],userAnswers:[],done:!1},a.getQuizSet=function(){var e=o[Math.floor(Math.random()*o.length)];Object(s.b)("/quiz/",{state:{interviewData:e}})},a}t=e,(a=n).prototype=Object.create(t.prototype),a.prototype.constructor=a,a.__proto__=t;var d=n.prototype;return d.componentDidMount=function(){var e=this;void 0!==this.props.location.state.done&&this.setState(function(){return{doneQuizData:e.props.location.state.doneQuizData,userAnswers:e.props.location.state.userAnswers,done:e.props.location.state.done}})},d.render=function(){var e=this.state.userAnswers;return i.a.createElement(r.a,null,i.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},i.a.createElement(s.a,{to:"/"},"Home"),i.a.createElement("div",{onClick:this.getQuizSet},"START"),!0===this.state.done&&i.a.createElement(i.a.Fragment,null,this.state.doneQuizData.map(function(a,t){return i.a.createElement("div",{key:t},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-sm-12"},a.question)),i.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-md-6"},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"preview-answer"},e[a.id]),i.a.createElement(l.a,{language:"javascript",style:c.a,showLineNumbers:!0,lineNumberStyle:{color:"#ff704d"}},e[a.id])),i.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-md-6"},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"preview-answer"},a.answer),i.a.createElement(l.a,{language:"javascript",style:c.a,showLineNumbers:!0,lineNumberStyle:{color:"#ff704d"}},a.example),i.a.createElement("div",{className:"preview-answer"},a.tip))))})),i.a.createElement("div",null,"Salut de pe quiz1!"),i.a.createElement("div",null,"Salut de pe quiz2!"),i.a.createElement("div",null,"Salut de pe quiz3!")))},n}(i.a.Component);a.default=d},202:function(e,a,t){var n;e.exports=(n=t(204))&&n.default||n},203:function(e,a,t){"use strict";var n=t(0),i=t.n(n),s=t(77),r=t.n(s);t.d(a,"a",function(){return r.a}),t.d(a,"b",function(){return s.navigate});t(202),t(10).default.enqueue,i.a.createContext({})},204:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.r(a);t(19);var n=t(0),i=t.n(n),s=t(101);a.default=function(e){var a=e.location,t=e.pageResources;return t?i.a.createElement(s.a,Object.assign({location:a,pageResources:t},t.json)):null}},205:function(e,a,t){"use strict";var n=t(0),i=t.n(n),s=(t(203),function(){return i.a.createElement("nav",{className:"navbar navbar-expand-lg navbar-light bg-light"},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},i.a.createElement("a",{className:"navbar-brand",href:"#"},"Navbar"),i.a.createElement("button",{className:"navbar-toggler",type:"button","data-toggle":"collapse","data-target":"#navbarNavAltMarkup","aria-controls":"navbarNavAltMarkup","aria-expanded":"false","aria-label":"Toggle navigation"},i.a.createElement("span",{className:"navbar-toggler-icon"})),i.a.createElement("div",{className:"collapse navbar-collapse",id:"navbarNavAltMarkup"},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"navbar-nav"},i.a.createElement("a",{className:"nav-item nav-link active",href:"#"},"Home ",i.a.createElement("span",{className:"sr-only"},"(current)")),i.a.createElement("a",{className:"nav-item nav-link",href:"#"},"Features"),i.a.createElement("a",{className:"nav-item nav-link",href:"#"},"Pricing"),i.a.createElement("a",{className:"nav-item nav-link disabled",href:"#",tabIndex:"-1","aria-disabled":"true"},"Disabled")))))});t.e(0).then(t.t.bind(null,201,7));a.a=function(e){var a=e.children;return i.a.createElement(i.a.Fragment,null,i.a.createElement(s,null),a)}}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=component---src-pages-interview-quiz-js-12a2baced42e2a3fab61.js.map